Hello friends, welcome to another
weekly breakout stock video from House of Stock.
Like last week, this
week too we
want to talk about a stock from the ICICI Group.
Last week we talked about ICICI Products. This
week we will
talk about ICICI Lombard.
First of all, if you look at the weekly chart,
you will see that the stock is currently
trading around 1717
and this can be called its lifetime
high level. Last time
we
saw this at the beginning of ₹1000000. Just a
week ago we saw a breakout scenario here.
After spending time here, the stock is again
trading around 1717. Once I
look
at the monthly chart, you will see that we had already
seen a breakout scenario on the monthly chart a couple of months ago.
Here, a month after the breakout,
here this  It poses and is now
ready to raise its head once again. If
you look at the weekly chart again, you will
see that the stock is ready to
show higher levels in the coming days. The
first level that can be seen is up to
₹2000000. We can see levels up to
₹1500000